So, we pulled off to the side of the
road and we got out of the car and we're
standing there and we're watching this
thing just hover
>> and it's not making any sound at all.
Nothing. It's just completely silent.
>> A guy pulls up behind us, gets out of
the car, and he says, "What the heck is
that?"
>> And my dad said, "I don't know." And
then it went like that at at this
fantastic speed.
Like it went directly
away from us, but at a at a speed that
was like incalculable.
And we just stood there looking up into
the, you know, night sky thinking, is it
going to come back? Is it, you know,
some kind of experimental
jet? I mean, I I had never in my life
seen anything like it, and neither had
he. So, we get back in the car. We start
driving again, and we're silent.
>> Yeah.
>> And then I said to I said to him, "So,
should we call somebody? Should we like
call the cops or something?" And he
said, "And tell them what? We saw a
flying saucer and it flew away." He
said, "They're going to think we're
nuts."
>> Yeah. So, we didn't tell anybody until
the next day. We went home after the end
of the shift and we told my mom. She
said, "Oh, come on." And my dad said,
"I'm telling you, we saw a UFO."
>> And I've been thinking I was I was 17
years old and I'm 60 now
>> and I still think about it all the time.
>> Yeah. You know, so some it affects
everyone differently. You know, I've
talked to people that say, "Oh, yeah,
that happened." And you know, no crazy
sighting too and like oh yeah that
happened at you know what's for dinner
>> but other people
>> they shrug their shoulders like I don't
I don't know what it is.
>> Yeah. And that's why I'm here and I I
have to tell you you know I had my
sighting in California and it was
something that baffled me. If I had a
camera I might have not thought to take
a picture. And I was in a hot tub and
the thing that the and there was no
bubbles and there was no sound. And
that's what freaked me out the most.
This thing was actually moving at a
steady pace and there was absolutely no
sound and I just couldn't understand why
there was no sound. Now I have to and I
called the cops and I got ridiculed, you
know.
>> See? Exactly. Exactly. You know, Jimmy
Carter when he was governor of Georgia,
he saw one and he called the cops and he
filed a report saying that it hovered in
the air. It was buzzing and they
ridiculed him and then they released the
report during the 1976 presidential
campaign just as a way to mock him and
make him sound like he was crazy.
>> Yeah. Well, I think they may have
explained what that is. There was some
type of failed launch or something, but
it's possible. It's possible. And I I
don't but I think even the grandson
agreed to it, you I mean, there was
something I watched, but still there's
so many more examples of people that
have seen these things. And the ridicule
factor is a lot less today than it was.
I'm sure you're aware of when the uh
Pentagon, you know, uh then 2000 2017
when the article came out in the New
York Times um with the videos and all
that that kind of changed the ridicule
factor. Yes. Way down. A lot of people
were convinced on the one hand or
silenced on the other.
>> You know, before we started the show
too, you and I were talking about
something something else. Um, when I was
a kid,
I had a lot of family here in the
Washington area. And so when I was a
kid, we used to come down to Washington
for summer vacations and stay with our
relatives. Well, my dad's cousin, who
was my godfather, owned a a very
prominent uh steakhouse in Oldtown
Alexandria, Virginia,
>> and he would get, you know, senators and
congressmen and bankers and politicians
uh you know, from the city. And it was
it was sort of a crossroads for movers
and shakers in Washington. and his son
who worked there as as a manager of the
restaurant had a friend who was there
one day when when I was there and he
happened to be an F-14 pilot. So, I'm
thinking this is 19
say 77 or 78 and um and he told us this
story. He just volunteered this story
that he was based at Langley Air Force
Base um in Norfick, Virginia.
>> Mh.
>> And he said all of the pilots had seen
these phenomena, whatever they were. In
fact, he had seen one. He followed it
for a while and it went down into the
water, it stayed down there for a while
and then it came back up. And he said he
was so rattled
that when he landed and reported it to
his superiors and some of the other
pilots, the other pilots have said, "Oh,
I've seen that. I've seen where they go
down into the water and come back up."
and he said he filed his his flight
report and nobody ever bothered to, you
know, ask him follow-up questions to
question, you know, was that really what
you saw or could it have been something
else? They just accepted it like, "Oh,
yeah, yeah, yeah. Everybody sees those."
They go down to the water, they come up
and I remember he said that it was
almost like the thing was drinking. It
went down into the water on purpose and
stayed down there and then came back up.
Did you describe a shape of any kind? Do
you remember?
>> He said that that was a a cylinder like
a Yeah, like a like a cigar is what he
said.
>> There's a lot of people describing
cigar- shaped, you know, UFOs and you
know, I mean, but that's the first one
I've heard of a cigar shape in the
water, but um you know, in and out of
the water, USO, UFO, USO, whatever you
want to call that one, but uh
fascinating. May I ask you a question?
>> Yeah.
>> I don't know if you happened to see uh
on Netflix, it was like Unsolved
Mysteries or It was one of these one of
these shows that Netflix just posted in
the last year and there was a very
detailed episode about these sightings
over Lake Michigan.
>> Um
>> Yes. Yes.
>> What do you make of that? because almost
all of the witnesses were employees of
the National Weather Service and not
only did they see them in the sky, but
they followed them on the radar
>> and those went down into the water. What
do you make of that?
>> I think there's really something to that
and that that the main person on that in
that uh episode was on my show and uh
like a year before he told me that he
was uh they had already filmed that
episode for Netflix. But I but uh anyway
there's he has a a total science mind
and was absolutely baffled by what he
was seeing there. So yeah, there was
really something to that and the same
thing, you know, Lake Michigan, another
big body of water.
>> And interestingly, they said that where
the lake had frozen, they avoided that
part.
>> They went over the the water that hadn't
frozen and then down into the water.
>> Yeah. Yeah, which is interesting too.
>> That is a great a great that that night
was a great great event that you really
don't hear a lot about. Matter of fact,
I until you just brought it up, I
basically haven't thought about that one
for for quite a while.
>> I was fascinated because it it lasted
for hours
>> and it wasn't just, you know, one guy
who may have been too tired while he
was, you know, on the job in the middle
of the night. It was like a dozen
different people and they all watched it
unfold on the radar as well.
>> Right. Right. Yeah, that's a that's a
real good one. I I have reached out to
and I can't think of his name right off
the bat. I've reached out to him again
after that aired. I'd like to talk to
him again about that. You know what? He
I think he received a lot of flack for
that. I do believe he did.
>> In fact, he quit his job.
>> Yeah, that's right. Yeah. Which is
really sad. You know, there's a lot of
these uh situations you hear about
things like that. There was a situation
called JAL. I can't think of the name.
It was a Japanese airline cargo uh back
um I'm going to get the whole thing. I
haven't looked into that for quite a
while, but basically the pilot kept
seeing this large thing the size of like
a a battleship up in the sky like the
shape of a walnut. It was following them
and it was on radar and they saw it on
ground radar. He ended up getting a desk
job after that, you know, but eventually
enough people, you know, pulled for him
and got him back to flying again. But,
you know, you can't it's it's hard when
you report these things with someone
like him.
>> It is. It's hard when you report them.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Um, you know, we there's so
many things I'd like to talk to you
about, but uh, also I do want to just
touch on the whistleblowing part that
you did uh, at some point here in the
conversation. Again, that the the full
interview that we did about that is
going to be linked at the very end of
the show and down I can put it also in
the show notes as well. But, um, I want
to talk a little bit about drones
because that's that's kind of still such
a mystery. I mean, I'm I'm still kind of
baffled by it and I'm I don't really
know what I think about the explanations
I keep hearing out there and wondered
what you thought about that.
You know, at first I I was
well, at first I just assumed it was a
defense department exercise of some
sort. And I have a friend who happens to
be a New Jersey state trooper. He said
that they were working under the
impression that there was a DOE or DoD
cargo that went missing, that perhaps it
was nuclear, perhaps it was maybe a
weapon of some sort or a missile and the
convoy, you know, lost the the
18-wheeler. I don't know. He said that's
what he thought it was. That's what he
had been told it was. But then there was
a there was a piece a segment on 60
Minutes just a couple of weeks ago or a
week ago maybe where they interviewed uh
these uh the the current and the former
commanding generals from uh
oh it was I think it was Langley
actually
>> Langley Air Force.
>> Right. Yes. And they said that,
you know, people think we can just shoot
these things down, but they're so small
that you can't use a a fighter jet to
shoot something that is so small and is
guided by hand. So their their
conclusions were that they were um
hostile
uh likely Chinese. Mhm.
>> U there happened to be a Chinese ship
off the coast of of New Jersey at least
for a little while while these things
were flying around and he said we we
have to come up with a better system to
protect ourselves. We can protect
ourselves against incoming ICBMs for
example.
>> Yeah.
>> But we can't protect ourselves against
drones.
>> Right. And but the the thing of it is is
that it's worldwide too. That's another
real puzzle.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, and these things are happening
like every year around the same time. It
was happening as well over the last
several years. There was an event in
Colorado a few years ago that was
baffling to everyone out there. I don't
know if you heard about that,
>> but um but then there's these really
largeiz drones and they're going for
>> Yeah.
>> You know, uh for extended amounts of
time, you know, so it's it's just
>> Yeah. It's still